CURRICULUM VITAE - LUKAS ROSENBERGER

CONTACT DATA:

Address: Mühlweg 10

9560 Feldkirchen

Austria

Telephone: +43664 1644190

Email: lukas.rosenberger@hotmail.com

Portfolio: http://mr-rossi.github.io/



PERSONAL SUMMARY: Lukas Rosenberger is a Computer Science student, currently in his 3rd

semester at the University of Applied Sciences Salzburg. He is studying MultiMediaTechnology, a modern blend of Computer Science and Media Technologies with a major focus on Video Game Engineering and Computer Vision. Lukas is a passionate programmer who enjoys acquiring new knowledge and likes to keep up with the newest developments, thinking about how they could improve current

technology.

DATE OF BIRTH: 06 March 1994

EDUCATION:

09/2014 - University of Applied Sciences Salzburg

MultiMediaTechnology

09/2008 - 07/2013 SECONDARY TECHNICAL VOCATIONAL COLLEGE AND INSTITUTE FOR

Research and Technology Villach

Department for Computer Sciences

Matura (with diploma)

Diploma: "SAP-Transaktionen vom Smartphone aus" (SAP transactions

on smartphones)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

07/2016 - 12/2016 **INTERNSHIP (GAME DEVELOPMENT)**

Arkavis, Bangkok, Thailand

2015 SWITCH-APP

University of Natural Resources and Life Sciences, Vienna

07/2013 - 01/2014 **MILITARY SERVICE**

Hensel-Kaserne, Villach

Supanz GmbH

Developing a mobile app to execute transactions in SAP systems

2009 - 2011 VARIOUS INTERNSHIPS

Lukas Rosenberger - +436641644190 - <u>lukas.rosenberger@hotmail.com</u> - <u>http://mr-rossi.github.io/</u>

CURRENT EXPERTISE:

Proficient in C++, C#, Java HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP; SQL, Oracle, SAP+ABAP;

Modern OpenGL, including Shader Programming in GLSL

Computer Vision

Basic 3D-modeling in Maya Linear Algebra and Statistics Software Architecture and Design Algorithms and Datastructures

Video Game Engineering

Knowledge of Web Based Technologies including HTML and CSS,

Databases, node.js

PERSONAL:

Nationality: Austrian

Languages: German (native),

English (First Certificate in English Grade A - C1),

Italian (basics)

Hobbies: 3D printing, Video Games, Pen&Paper RPGs

PERSONAL STATEMENT:

As an avid gamer and technology geek getting to study

MultiMediaTechnology at the University of Applied Sciences Salzburg is the perfect way of extending my personal hobbies into my future work

life.

I enjoy developing solutions to difficult problems and finding ways to improve on existing concepts. I can easily get excited about almost any kind of game project and will try to do everything possible to make games a great experience.

My focus is on game development and game design and I'm always trying to stay on top of new developments in those topics.

Currently I have worked on several games, which you can find on my website http://mr-rossi.github.io/.

Ahrly